I ate seven pints of ice cream this week
and was still in a caloric deficit.
Here's how I did it. I used my Ninja
Creamy to recreate my favorite ice cream
flavors, but low calorie and high
protein. Here are five of the recipes I
made this week. I started off by
recreating McDonald's Oreo McFlurry, and
this did not disappoint. In fact, it was
so good that I decided to make it in the
chocolate version, which McDonald's
doesn't even have. And this one packed
over 30 g of protein. Then I decided to
switch it up. I made a Cinnabon inspired
cinnamon bun ice cream with almost 50
grams of protein. Then I was feeling
like chocolate again and I did a
chocolate peanut butter cup ice cream
and this was the perfect combination of
sweet and salty. Also, I've been seeing
this protein coke float root beer float
thing all over Tik Tok. So, I decided to
recreate that into a protein ice cream.
And that's all for the week.